scottsigler.com 2019-10-22

# Privacy Policy

EMPTY SET ENTERTAINMENT  
PRIVACY POLICY

Updated: June 22, 2018

Empty Set Entertainment, LLC (“we,” “us,” “our,” and “Empty Set Entertainment”) takes seriously the private nature of your personal information. This privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you give us when you use this website or purchase our products or services. Please take time to read this policy carefully.

Empty Set Entertainment is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We love the Sigler “Junkies” and would never intentionally harm any of you. Besides, with Scott writing two books a year and A managing Scott, we barely had time to update this policy to comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). We have neither time or desire to sell your information.

Empty Set Entertainment may change this policy from time to time by updating this page, and reserves the right to do so. Such revisions shall be effective immediately upon posting. Your continued participation on this website indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and of the collection, use, disclosure, and management, and retention of Your personal information as described herein. We recommend that You review this Privacy Policy periodically so that You are aware of any changes.

We are subject to the investigatory and enforcement power of the Federal Trade Commission (“FTC”) in the United States, which oversees acts or practices in or affecting commerce by any person, partnership, or corporation.

**What Information We Collect**  
We may collect the following information:  
• Name  
• Contact information including email address, geographic coordinates, phone number, and physical address (for shipping of product purchased)  
• Demographic information such as postcode, preferences, and interests  
• Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

Empty Set Entertainment does not collect any other personally identifiable information that you do not expressly provide. We do not request or require sensitive or special category information about you, including:  
• Racial or ethnic origins  
• Political opinions  
• Religious or philosophical beliefs  
• Trade-union membership  
• Genetic data  
• Biometric data  
• Data regarding Your health, sex life, or sexual orientation  
• Criminal records  
• Credit history and creditworthiness

**What We Do with the Information We Gather**  
We collect personal information about and from you that is necessary for us to provide you the services that you request, to help serve your needs, to make customized offerings of our products and services for you, and to fulfill legal and regulatory requirements. Both the amount and type of information collected will be limited to that which is necessary to fulfill these purposes. The purpose for collecting this data is to provide you the products and services you requested from us.

We collect and hold your information as long as reasonably necessary to give effect to these purposes. At any time, you may request that we update, correct, or delete your personal information, and we will comply with such requests as permitted by law or contract. You may also request a copy of the personal information we have for you and information about how we are using it unless we are required or authorized by law to withhold such information.

**Consent to Receive Marketing Communications**  
By purchasing one of our products or services, you gave consent for us to contact you regarding that product or service as part of our commitment to customer service.

If you opt-in to receive marketing emails from us, you voluntarily consent to receive such messages. You may contact us regarding this use at anytime using the contact information below.

We shall keep your information on our mailing list until you withdraw your Consent. You may opt out of receiving these messages at any time. We do not share this information with any third parties outside Empty Set Entertainment, except as stated below.

**Sharing Information with Others**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via registration, email, or other direct contact from you.

We share personal information about you, as required or permitted by law, with third parties, such as service providers, who assist us in the day-to-day operations of Empty Set Entertainment. We require third-party service providers to enter into confidentiality agreements with us, prohibiting them from using any personal information they obtain for any other purpose other than those for which they were retained or as permitted by law. We acknowledge that under the GDPR, we are liable in cases of onward transfers to third parties.

We will not share, distribute, lease, or sell Your information with other third parties without your explicit consent except as stated herein. We may share your information with a third party if we have a good-faith belief that sharing the information is necessary to comply with a law, regulation, or enforceable government request including court orders; to investigate potential violations or technical issues on our website; or to protect against harm to us, our users, or our affiliates’ rights, property, safety, or to the public as permitted by law. We must disclose your personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

For all other uses, we will ask your permission to use your personal information in a way that is not directly related to the reason that we collected it and we do not have relevant current permission from you unless so permitted by law.

**Processing Payments**  
We use a third party to process payments from customers who purchase goods or services. We never have access to your credit card information. The processing of your payment is performed according to the payment processing company’s terms of service and privacy policy.

**Transmitting Your Information Overseas**  
We are based in the United States. When we transmit a person’s personal information from overseas, we will only do so because you’ve subscribed to our email list, to join our online community, or purchased a product or service from us. Placing an order for products or services that requires you to voluntarily provide us with your personal information is an expression of consent to your personal information being sent overseas as part of the transaction process.

Pursuant to the GDPR, we use reasonable efforts to comply with the requirements of the EU-US Privacy Shield.

**Your Rights Regarding Your Information**  
At any time, you may request that we update, correct, or delete your personal information, and we will comply with such requests as permitted by law or contract. You may also request a copy of the personal information we have for you and information about how we are using it, and we will comply with such requests unless we are required or authorized by law to withhold such information. If we receive such a request, we suspect the results will be bland, as we are completely transparent with what we do with your information. We have no intent to misuse anyone information and take the trust you put in us seriously.

Under California Civil Code § 1798.83-1798.84, California residents may ask us for information about the categories of data we collected about them and shared with third parties for marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and provide the contact information for those third parties. If you are a California resident who would like a copy of such information, please send us a written request using our contact information below.

In accordance with the GDPR, you may lodge a complaint with the appropriate supervisory authority at any time.

**Links to Other Websites**  
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites. Providing a link, however, is not an endorsement. We shall not be responsible for any material on any site to which we provide a link that we did not create.

You assume all risk by following a link. Once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we provide no guarantee that any website it links to will be accurate or available, and we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites. These sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy policy applicable to the website in question.

**Security**  
We have internal policies and procedures designed to protect your personal information, including protection from unauthorized use or disclosure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and to maintain the confidentiality and integrity of the personal information we collect from you. We continue to assess new technology as it becomes available and to upgrade our physical and electronic security systems as appropriate. In accordance with GDPR, we perform a self-assessment of our privacy practices and procedures at least annually.

Our policy is to permit third parties to access your personal information only if they have a business purpose for using such information, such as administering, providing, or developing our products or services. These third parties are provided with your personal information on a need-to-know basis only and are bound by contract to keep all personal information confidential and protect such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We delete personal information that is no longer necessary for us to have as a business entity or to provide you with our products and services.

**How We Use Cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. We examine the information regarding aggregate usage and volume data from all visitors, which does not include anyone’s personal information. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages people visit. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. If you turn off cookies, you may still access this website, but this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Contact Us**  
Please contact us with inquiries or complaints or to request access to, or correction of, your personal information held by us at info@emptyset.com.
